Guide to the Charles F. Sweet papers, 1953-1990.
Sweet, Charles F. papers, 1953-1990.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Charles F. Sweet papers, 1953-1990.
4827
Charles F. Sweet
9.4 cubic ft.
Correspondence, reports, subject files, and personal and professional papers.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence, reports, subject files, and personal and professional papers; includes an article: "Economic Transition of the Socialist Republic of Vietnam." Also, "Vietnam Files" and computer printouts; and records of the regional plan and development of the Arusha Region of Tanzania.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Cornell University graduate, planning and management consultant, professor.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence, reports, subject files, and personal and professional papers; includes an article: "Economic Transition of the Socialist Republic of Vietnam." Also, "Vietnam Files" and computer printouts; and records of the regional plan and development of the Arusha Region of Tanzania.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Sweet, Charles F.
Subjects:
Planning--Tanzania--Arusha.
Places:
Vietnam--Economic conditions.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Economic Transition in the Socialist Republic of Vietnam by Charles F. Sweet and Ruy Y. Moreno, 1960 (Box 1)
- Student Organizations (Box 2, Folder 1)
- New School Movement (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Vietnamese Youth - Publicity (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Liberty Youth Camp (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Youth Leaders Conference, July 1965 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Summer Youth Program [SYP] Reports III, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Flood Relief Effort, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- RAND Debriefing - Youth (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Vietnamese Youth - bio-data (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Youth Leaders (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Vietnamese Youth - Miscellaneous (Box 2, Folder 11)
- SYP - Finances, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 12-13)
- SYP Vietnamese Reports II, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- SYP Vietnamese Reports III, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- SYP American Reports I, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- SYP American Reports II, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Viet-Nam - Hamlet/Village Organization (Box 2, Folder 18)
- United States Officials: Statements (Box 2, Folder 19)
- National Student Association (NSA) Visit to Viet-Nam (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Training Documents (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Negotiations (Box 2, Folder 22)
- United States Organization (Box 2, Folder 23)
- SYP Vietnamese Reports I, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 24-25)
- Viet-Nam History (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Young - Southeast Asia Project (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Viet-Nam Maps (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Viet-Nam - Biographies (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Nation-Building in South Viet-Nam (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Viet-Nam Music (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Viet-Nam Humor (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Viet-Nam Slides (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Viet-Nam - Chieu Hoi (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Vietnamese Viewpoint (Box 2, Folder 35)
- GVN Propaganda (Box 2, Folder 36)
- [H.R. 15750 - an Act to amend further the Foreign Assistance Act of 1961, ...] (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Aid (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Vietnamese Society (Box 2, Folder 39)
- New Life Construction Project (Box 2, Folder 40-41)
- Viet-Nam - Economics (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Viet-Nam - Policy Statements (Box 2, Folder 43-44)
- Viet-Nam - Background Notes (State) (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Viet-Nam - Military (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Viet-Cong (Box 2, Folder 47-48)
- Viet-Nam - Post-War Planning (Box 2, Folder 49)
- A Vietnamese Revolution (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Viet-Nam - Land Reform (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Viet-Nam - Ministries (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Moderator, Dec. 1966 (see p. 8) (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Long An II (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Editorial Comment (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Mission Youth Committee (Box 3, Folder 2)
- National Voluntary Service (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Youth Organizations (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Darnell - Papers (Box 3, Folder 5)
- [untitled] (Box 3, Folder 6)
- SYP, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Student Participation in Elections (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Vietnamese Culture (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Tet - Rand Corporation report, 1965-1968 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Memos - White House, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Lansdale on Soothsaying (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Memos (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Letters - Jan.-June 1965 [to family] (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Letters - July-Dec. 1965 [to family] (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Letters - Jan.-June 1966 [to family] (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Letters - July-Dec. 1966 [to family] (Box 3, Folder 17)
- National Liberation Front [NLF] (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Ministry of Youth (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Southeast Asia Development Advisory Group [SEADAG] Transferability Conference - I (Box 3, Folder 20-21)
- Editorial Comment I (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Lessons from China and a Strategy for Counter-Subversion (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Viet-Nam - Constitution (Box 3, Folder 24)
- College Applications (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Highland Tribes (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Lansdale Jottings (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Forum for Asian Political Development (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Nixon Policy Paper I (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Nixon Policy Paper II (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Nixon Policy Paper III (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Urban League Training Program (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Hawaiian Development Corporation (Box 3, Folder 33)
- United States Student Participation Elections, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Education and World Affairs Papers (Box 3, Folder 35-36)
- Revolution (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Newspaper Articles (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Newsletters (Box 3, Folder 39)
- International Voluntary Services [IVS] Seminars (Box 3, Folder 40)
- IVS Monthly Reports (Box 3, Folder 41)
- IVS Report (Box 3, Folder 42)
- [untitled] (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Youth Leadership Training (Box 3, Folder 44)
- SYP (background materials) (Box 3, Folder 45)
- SYP Provincial Reports, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 46-47)
- Viet-Nam - Refugees (Box 3, Folder 48)
- Viet-Nam - Administration (Box 3, Folder 49)
- Viet-Nam - Organization (Box 3, Folder 50)
- Viet-Nam - Pacification I (Box 3, Folder 51-52)
- Viet-Nam - Pacification II (Box 3, Folder 53-54)
- IVS Newsletters (Box 3, Folder 55-56)
- Letters, 1969-1978 (Box 3, Folder 57)
- Provincial Reports (Box 3, Folder 58)
- Pacification II (Box 3, Folder 59)
- Long An II (Box 3, Folder 60)
- Viet-Nam - Religion (Box 3, Folder 61)
- Untitled [Miscellany, including family letters from Sweet, reports, IVS newsletters, 1964-1966 ] (Box 4, Folder 1-4)
- Letters - Jan.-Mar. 1968 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Lansdale Articles (Box 4, Folder 6)
- RAND Study - Viet Cong (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Hudson Institute - Viet-Nam Policy Papers (Box 4, Folder 8-9)
- Untitled [Viet-Nam Miscellaneous] (Box 4, Folder 10-11)
- Lansdale on Tet/Lansdale on Cao Dai (Box 4, Folder 12-13)
- Lansdale on leaked report re: elections (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Tet Analysis (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Letters of Commendation (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Lansdale - Pre-Tet (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Cold War Intelligence Requirements (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Viet Cong and Youth/Alliance Organization (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Order of Battle (Nixon Policy Paper III) (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Long An I (Box 4, Folder 21)
- North Viet-Nam (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Provincial Reports (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Untitled (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Office of Youth Affairs (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Development Alternatives, Inc. [DAI], 1971 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- DAI and Miscellaneous, 1968-1971 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- DAI, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Carver - Real Revolution in South Viet-Nam (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Pacification Attitude Analysis System [PAAS] surveys (Box 5)
- PAAS [old] - surveys (Box 6)
- Arusha Region - General (Box 7, Folder 1-10)
- "Arusha Region: Health Sector Assessment by P. Stanley Yoder for Development Alternatives, Inc." (DAI) (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Arusha Region Development Plan (Box 7, Folder 12-13)
- Arumeru District (Box 7, Folder 14-18)
- Hanang District - Kiru Valley (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Hanang District (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Kiteto District (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Mbulu District (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Mbulu District; Massai reports by Henry Fosbrooke for DAI (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Mbulu District (Box 7, Folder 24-25)
- Monduli District (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Ngorongoro District (Box 7, Folder 27-28)
- Tanzania, Northern (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Annual Plan, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Cornell University, Report on Evaluation Visit to the APVDP Graduate Training Programme in Regional Planning at (Box 7, Folder 31)
- "Development Alternatives, Inc.," by Henry Fosbrooke (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Development Project, Arusha Planning and Village, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- Issue Abstracts in English and Swahili, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 34-36)
- Planning Framework, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 37)
- Project Proposals, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 38)
- Regional Planning Committee Meeting, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 39)
- "Sector Assistant of Tourism in the Arusha Region of Tanzania" by Victoria A. Morse (Box 7, Folder 40)
- Guideline for the Preparation of the Regional Estimates for the 1981-82 Financial Year (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Sudan Rural Development Planning Project Trip Report, by Mike Sarco (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Union Five-Year Development Plan (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Women and Development: A Case Study of Ten Tanzanian Villages, by Liz Wily (Box 8, Folder 4-6)
- Arusha Planning and Village Development Project - Fourth Annual Plan - 1982-1983, Mar. 1, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Arusha Planning and Village Development Project - Eighth Quarter Progress Report, June 30, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Arusha Planning and Village Development Project - Ninth Quarter Progress Report, Sept. 30, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Arusha Planning and Village Development Project - Tenth Quarter Progress, Dec. 31, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Arusha Planning and Village Development Project - A Discussion Paper Written by Donald S. Humpal, DAI Staff Agriculturist for AP/VDP & RIDEP - Arusha, May 1980 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Center and Periphery in Arusha Region: Institutional Capacities and Development Initiatives in the Context of Existing Governmental Structures and Village Organization, by Garry L. Thomas, DAI, Nov. 1980 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Proposed Dongobesh Gravity Rural Water Supply Scheme, prepared by Arusha Regional Water Department and Arusha Planning and Village Development Project for Regional Development Directorate, Arusha (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Encouraging Village Self-Reliance in Arumeru District, Tanzania, by Joyce Stanley (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Hainu River Study Pre-Feasibility Report, TANESCO, APVDP, Dec. 1980 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- The Livestock Sector in Arusha, by I.C. Walton, Dec. 1980 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Livestock, Wildlife and Land Use Survey, Arusha Region, Tanzania, Final Report, Volume 2: Figures and Tables (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Prime Minister's Office - Arusha Planning and Village Development Project - 2nd Annual Work Plan, July 1980-June 1981 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Prime Minister's Office - Road Priority Determination Arusha Region, Report prepared by Dr. Benno J. Ndulu, June 1981 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- The Status and Utilization of Wildlife in Arusha Region, Tanzania (Box 8, Folder 20)
- The Village Profile Exercise - Background Information, Impressions and Perceptions for Arusha Planning and Village Development Project and the Regional Development Directorate, Arusha, by D.D. Peterson and T.T. Peterson, June 1980 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- An Assessment of the Revenue Generation Capabilities of Villages, Districts and Arusha Region: Some Policy Options, July 1981, with Executive Summary (Box 9)
- Arusha Region Integrated Development Plan, Sept. 1981
  - Volume One - Arusha Region Today: 1981 (Box 9)
  - Volume Two - Development Strategies and Priorities for the Next 20 Years (Box 9)
  - Volume Three - Region Medium-Term Plan 1981/1982-1985/1986 (Box 9)
  - Volume Four - Major Areas for Long-Term Investments (Box 9)
  - Volume Five - Information Strategy and Documentation (Box 9)
- The Financial Infrastructure in Tanzania: Perspectives, Problems and Policy Strategies with Policy and Program Implications for Arusha Region, Aug. 1981 (Box 9)